

# CONTACT

- 09706340680
- Virac Catanduanes
- https://mico322.github.io/ micotubice/

### **EDUCATION**

## 2020 - 2024 CATANDUANES STATE UNIVERSITY

 Bachelor Of Science In Information System

## 2014 - 2020 CALATAGAN HIGH SCHOOL

- Information and Communication Technology
- Completed 2 years in Computer System Servicing NC II

## **SKILLS**

- Programming Languages: Java,
  Python, C++
- Data Management: Data Entry, Analysis, and Visualization
- Computer Vision: Introductory Knowledge
- Tools: Adobe Photoshop, Data Management Systems

# MICO TUBICE

# **PROFILE**

With a keen eye for detail and precision in data entry and management, I bring over years of experience in Adobe Photoshop to seamlessly blend creativity with meticulous organization. My ability to tackle challenges with efficiency and innovation ensures exceptional performance in both graphic design and data entry tasks.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Freelance - Onlinejob.ph

APR 2022 - JUN 2024

Native Ad Specialist & Personal Assistant

- Optimized post settings for better content performance.
- Integrated high-quality images from Pixabay.
- Managed advertising campaigns for major brands like Amazon and Netflix.
- · Created custom thumbnails and videos to support ad strategies.
- Managed and organized large volumes of data for advertising campaigns.
- Handled detailed data entry tasks for campaign performance tracking.

#### Freelance - Onlinejob.ph

April 2024- May 2024

Product Label Designer

- Designed and developed 20 unique candy product labels.
- Managed the entire design process from concept to final production.
- Adhered to brand guidelines, ensuring precision and attention to detail.
- Organized and maintained data for each product category and flavor.

#### CERTIFICATES

- Programming Java NC III | Joysis Tech Voc Inc | 2021 2022
- Computer Systems Servicing NC II | 2019 2019